inmyarea.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy | In My Area

## This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which we collect, use, maintain and disclose information collected from visitors to this website.

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an order or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

We may also collect non-personal identification information about website visitors whenever they interact with our website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about visitors’ means of connection to our site such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To improve our website.

(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)

  * To process transactions.

(Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)

  * To send periodic emails.

(The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.)

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser [if you allow] that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.)

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential (which may include credit card and other information that they collect directly from you). We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Links from this website**

We do not monitor or review the content of other parties’ websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or materials appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. This Company will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.

 **Terms Relating to Google**

This Site utilizes the Google Maps API(s) and by visiting and using the Site's services and applications, you are also agreeing to be bound by the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

 **Consumer Brands, LLC**  
65 Enterprise  
Aliso Viejo, CA 92656  
949-356-1315

 _Effective as of September 28, 2012_
  *[949-356-1315]: Phone
